<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<body>
    <content>
        
        <title>Boac</title>
        <welcome>Welcome to Boac</welcome>

        <description>Boac is the capital municipality of the province of Marinduque, located in the Philippines. It is situated on the southern part of the island of Marinduque, which is part of the MIMAROPA region. Boac serves as the center of commerce, government, and culture in the province. The town of Boac has a rich historical and cultural heritage. It is known for its well-preserved Spanish colonial architecture, which can be seen in its old houses and structures. The Boac Cathedral, also known as the Cathedral of the Immaculate Conception, is a prominent landmark in the town. It is a beautiful church made of coral stones and serves as a testament to the town's religious significance. The landscape of Boac is characterized by rolling hills, lush greenery, and a river that runs through the town. The Boac River is not only a scenic spot but also an important waterway for the locals. It is a source of livelihood for fishermen and is often used for transportation and irrigation purposes. The people of Boac are predominantly Tagalog speakers and are known for their warm and friendly nature. The town celebrates various festivals throughout the year, with the Boac Town Fiesta being one of the most anticipated events. During this celebration, the streets come alive with colorful parades, street dances, and other cultural activities. In terms of economic activities, Boac is primarily an agricultural town. Rice, coconut, and citrus fruits are some of the main crops grown in the area. Fishing is also an important industry, given its proximity to the sea and the Boac River. Overall, Boac in Marinduque offers a mix of historical, cultural, and natural attractions. It provides visitors with a glimpse into the province's past and showcases its vibrant present. Whether it's exploring its colonial architecture, enjoying the scenic landscapes, or immersing oneself in the local festivities, Boac offers a unique experience for travelers.</description>

        <button>Home</button>

    </content>
</body>