<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<body>
    <content>
        
        <title>Sta Cruz</title>
        <welcome>Welcome to Sta Cruz</welcome>

        <description>Santa Cruz is a municipality in the province of Marinduque, located in the Philippines. It is situated on the southeastern part of the island of Marinduque, which is part of the MIMAROPA region. Santa Cruz is known for its beautiful beaches, historical landmarks, and vibrant culture. One of the main attractions in Santa Cruz is the scenic Poctoy White Beach. This white sand beach with crystal-clear waters is a popular destination for locals and tourists alike. Visitors can relax on the beach, swim in the inviting waters, or engage in water sports and activities. Poctoy White Beach offers a serene and picturesque setting for those seeking a beach getaway. Santa Cruz is also known for its historical sites. The Santa Cruz Church, officially known as the Immaculate Conception Parish Church, is a notable landmark in the municipality. This centuries-old church showcases Spanish colonial architecture and is considered a significant religious and cultural site. The church has been well-preserved and is a testament to Santa Cruz's historical heritage. Another historical attraction in Santa Cruz is the Boac-Malbog Bridge. This old bridge connects the towns of Santa Cruz and Boac and is an iconic symbol of the province. It provides a scenic view of the surrounding river and mountains, making it a favorite spot for photography enthusiasts. The municipality celebrates various festivals and events throughout the year. One of the most prominent celebrations is the Santa Cruzan Festival, which takes place in May. This religious and cultural festival honors the Blessed Virgin Mary and features a grand procession of beautifully adorned floats and participants dressed in traditional attire. Santa Cruz's economy is primarily based on agriculture, with farming and fishing being the main industries. Rice, coconut, and citrus fruits are among the main agricultural products in the area. Fishing is also a significant livelihood for many residents, given its coastal location and proximity to the sea. The people of Santa Cruz are known for their warm hospitality and strong community spirit. They take pride in their cultural heritage and actively participate in preserving their traditions and customs. Overall, Santa Cruz in Marinduque offers a combination of natural beauty, historical landmarks, and cultural experiences. Whether it's enjoying the pristine beaches, exploring the historical sites, or immersing oneself in the local festivities, Santa Cruz provides a unique and enriching destination for visitors.</description>

        <button>Home</button>

    </content>
</body>